// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
  {
    numb: 1,
    question: "true + false",
    answer: "1",
    options: ["truefalse", "1", "NaN", "Syntax Error"],
  },
  {
    numb: 2,
    question: "[,,,].length",
    answer: "3",
    options: ["0", "3", "4", "Syntax Error"],
  },
  {
    numb: 3,
    question: "[1, 2, 3] + [4, 5, 6]",
    answer: '"1,2,34,5,6"',
    options: ['"123456"', '"1,2,34,5,6"', '"1,2,3,4,5,6"', "NaN"],
  },
  {
    numb: 4,
    question: "0.2 + 0.1 === 0.3",
    answer: "false",
    options: ["true", "false", "NaN", "Syntax Error"],
  },
  {
    numb: 5,
    question: "10,2",
    answer: "2",
    options: ["10.2", "2", "10", "20"],
  },
  {
    numb: 6,
    question: '!!""',
    answer: "false",
    options: ["false", "undefined", "true", "Syntax Error"],
  },
  {
    numb: 7,
    question: "+!![]",
    answer: "1",
    options: ["true", "false", "1", "0"],
  },
  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "!!!true",
    answer: "false",
    options: ["SyntaxError", "true", "0", "false"],
  },
  {
    numb: 9,
    question: 'true == "true"',
    answer: "false",
    options: ["false", "true", "undefined", "Syntax Error"],
  },
  {
    numb: 10,
    question: "010 - 03",
    answer: "5",
    options: ["7", "3", "NaN", "5"],
  },
  {
    numb: 11,
    question: '" - - ""',
    answer: "0",
    options: ['""', "0", "NaN", "Syntax Error"],
  },
  {
    numb: 12,
    question: "null + 0",
    answer: "0",
    options: ["null0", "0", "NaN", "Type Error"],
  },
  {
    numb: 13,
    question: "0/0",
    answer: "NaN",
    options: ["0", "Syntax Error", "NaN", "Infinity"],
  },
  {
    numb: 14,
    question: "1/0 > Math.pow(10, 1000)",
    answer: "false",
    options: ["false", "true", "NaN", "0"],
  },
  {
    numb: 15,
    question: "true++",
    answer: "SyntaxError",
    options: ["0", "NaN", "SyntaxError", "1"],
  },
  {
    numb: 16,
    question: '"" - 1',
    answer: "-1",
    options: ["1", "0", "-1", "'-1'"],
  },
  {
    numb: 17,
    question: '(null - 0) + "0"',
    answer: '"00"',
    options: ["00", "0", "NaN", '"00"'],
  },
  {
    numb: 18,
    question: 'true + ("true" - 0)',
    answer: "NaN",
    options: ["2", "1", "Syntax Error", "NaN"],
  },
  {
    numb: 19,
    question: "!5 + !5",
    answer: "0",
    options: ["5", "0", "NaN", "1"],
  },
  {
    numb: 20,
    question: "[] + []",
    answer: '""',
    options: ['""', "[]", "[,]", "NaN"],
  },
  {
    numb: 21,
    question: "NaN === NaN",
    answer: "false",
    options: ["false", "NaN", "true", "Type Error"],
  },
  {
    numb: 22,
    question: "NaN++",
    answer: "NaN",
    options: ["true", "NaN", "TypeError", "undefined"],
  },
  {
    numb: 23,
    question: "undefined + false",
    answer: "NaN",
    options: ["0", "undefinedfalse", "NaN", "Infintiy"],
  },
  {
    numb: 24,
    question: "+0 === -0",
    answer: "true",
    options: ["0", "NaN", "true", "Type Error"],
  },
  {
    numb: 25,
    question: '+!!NaN * "" - - [,]',
    answer: "0",
    options: ["0", '"0"', "NaN", "I dont know"],
  },
];
